[{"answer": "It's like pasta.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "ISPIRITO: It looks like chocolates, it looks like the worst food you can eat, right?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Let's see if the audience can guess how many calories in all of these foods.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What was the total calorie?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "500.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Tangerine, how many?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "50.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Andrei, how many?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "So, this a high protein chocolate smoothy.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Well, what it actually was?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Well, normally, the pasta is made with flour which is almost 300 calories in and of itself.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "And normally, you assume a lot of calories, right?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "OK, so that would be about 710.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "How many calories?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "It's an unbelievably difficult question to answer, but I think what we're doing right now is part of it.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "How do you culturally change that kind of thinking and the fast food epidemic and so on to get them to start to cook at home in a way that can produce this kind of result?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "I'll tell you what, the reasons I got obvious is my sex wasn't as good as it should be.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "You have better sex or your food, Rocco?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "I'm 46 years old.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "One (ph) faster, so, how old are you?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "You're 6 foot, 1 right?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Almost 230, 228, yeah.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "You were -- your heaviest, how much?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "I was 35 years old, and I was already being told that I'm in health danger of heart disease.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "And what did you do?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "40 pounds and -- so if a chubby chef with crooked spine and flat feet, who could totally get away with it, by the way.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "You lost how much?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "I'm doing great, Piers.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Jared, how are you?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "So, you're this unknown guy who just announced he'd been eating a lot of Subways and had lost a lot of weight.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "I do, you know, I don't eat it every single day anymore, but I've learned a lot, you know, in my -- exactly in moderation.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Do you still eat Subway sandwiches?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "Piers, my heaviest weight was 320.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "What do you know?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "So, I was like a business guy running around the world, doing deals focused on building companies.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "And how do you do this?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "So, the first thing I'd say, Piers, is I didn't look at what I did as a diet.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "How have you managed to stay so disciplined?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "I don't know if it's so much you, but I felt like I needed a different perspective.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Why did you want to do that, why do you want to become me?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "I've never been overweight, never struggled.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Because you've never been fat, right?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "I think some people look at me differently.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Is there something you find that that wasn't happening if (inaudible) you've lost it?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "No one was really mean, but I felt like, from my perspective, people were staring at me more.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Oh, Drew, you've lost it, right?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "I've heard so often people trying to blame of people for those problem.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "How do we change the thinking?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "From the stories that I hear, it's very clear that people are addicted to sugar.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Why are you seeing so much business, you think, form the stories that you get?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Well, our whole country is desperate.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "When it gets to that stage, people are pretty desperate, aren't they, to do something?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "And the reality of it is it's making you sick whether you have a weight problem or not.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "How we get through this?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "I'm great.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Tracy, how are you?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "So every time I see one of these celebrities having a baby, within about three months, they look like (inaudible).", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "You know what, I support them.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "What do you do to these poor women?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Well that's a little surprise actually.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "I think we gave then -- didn't we give them DVD's?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Well, right now Kim (ph) is doing what she should be doing which is bonding with her baby.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "What are the key things that women who've had a baby need to do quite quickly to get rid of the baby fat and so on?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Yeah, that's a really great question, because the formula is key and the ratio is key and also enjoying life is key.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "What kind of workout should you be doing and what kind of diet should you combine it with, if you want to just get some reasonable results, you know, maybe lose 89 pounds or whatever it may be?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Good question.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "What is it about your Barry's Bootcamp that is different to others?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Both.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "It's the best combination, both?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "It's indoor cycling.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Now, what is it and how does it work?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's the main thing.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "How do you get people into right discipline, to keep going and not just give up after a few weeks because so many people do?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "What's unique about it is that, you know, well, first of all, I'd like to say that people are afraid to workout and because they think it's so hard.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "And what is unique about this?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "A modifier, if someone so -- if I'm doing crazy high jumps, there's a modifier doing a less low impact.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "What is a modifier?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Actually, that's a good question because I'm a believer in the hour workout.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "And how many times a week to get reasonably fit?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "You know, if I can also say, it has to be fun.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "Barry, you want to get a free plug-in while you're on it?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "It's a bike.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "So, this is like a bike, right?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "I want you to look at that little screen and I want you to take your torque to 25.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "hen what happens?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "Until it gets to 25.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "his one?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "You're at 25, right?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "Easy.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 744, "question": "You good?", "qSentId": 743}, {"answer": "It's easy (ph).", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 753, "question": "How's that going?", "qSentId": 752}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 757, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 756}, {"answer": "About 30.", "docId": "140110pmt", "aSentId": 763, "question": "And how many seconds we'll have to keep doing this for?", "qSentId": 762}]